Hello friends, welcome to Market Pani YouTube
channel. I am Advocate
Jitendra. Friends, in today's video we will
learn that whenever we have to
transfer ownership, the meaning of any game is to get it
transferred, then does it
require insurance or not, but
friends, it is also very clear like from
where the transfer takes place,
what documents are required in the Ashram, so let us
see one by one, friends, first of all, to get the
RC transferred, you will have to go to the party in which
your registered party was registered, that is, the party where the
vehicle was stolen, you will have to give
some phone numbers to the happy
women, they will give whatever
they have, after that your vehicle gets
transferred to a new name, so for this you
can go to the transport department's website, you
can submit it here and then
click there, friends, it is
different
everywhere, but the
need for some documents or some other things
varies according to different zodiac signs,
so you should find out once in your mind Fantastic,
friends, what documents have to be given, then in
almost all the countries
you can get the most from it.  First a
copy of the RC is required, after that there should be a pollution
certificate, you need your Ghaghra,
after that you will
need a photo of what you are doing here and what you are doing,
and both mean
proof of their address,
friends
what happens in different comments is that you are doing it to someone, do you
need a photo to be taken with the vehicle
or you can avoid this problem by talking to your local RTO once,
so friends now let's talk about the
need for an insurance company, so friends let me
tell you that
you cannot answer on your own, that
means you will need a vehicle, so you should have it,
you should have it,
now
friends, I have taken this,
then
you will have to get it done,
friends, without insurance the
money will not be transferred, so in whose name will it be,
now send the
Ghaghra,
so friends,
after that you will have to go here and after that it will be in
your name,
friends, you will try to
talk to this company and get your name registered in that policy
because there are many
people in their
name, so
friends, if you like this video, then
like, share and subscribe to the channel  Don't forget to do it
and if anyone else has played it then you
can ask in the comment section till then the war